There is a young couple - your wife beats you all the time.
Come out.
Prophecy Confirmation
My name is Ogbe Emmanuel.
I'm the one the man of God prophesied about that his wife always beats him.
Each time I and my wife have a little quarrel or I want to correct her,
she will not listen to me.
Just a little correction - she would beat me.
Two months ago, she beat me on the mouth and blood started gushing out.
She does not have affection for me.
Since I married her in 2015, I have never felt like a married man.
How does a married man feel?
They feel happy with their wives.
Prophecy Time
So, she used to beat you.
Yes. Very well, Man of God.
My name is Obiora Edith.
You used to beat your husband.
Yes, whenever I am angry, I slap him.
Prophecy Time
Most of the time, I get angry when I am close to him. I don't know why.
Get close to him and see whether you will be angry.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Our names are Mr and Mrs Obiora Emmanuel.
We thank God for the deliverance that God has given us last week, Sunday.
Last week Sunday, during the mass prayer, the man of God prophesied and pointed to my area.
He said there was a young people over there and the wife always beats the man.
Prophecy Testimony
I thought about it for a minute because I knew what was happening in my home.
Immediately, I jumped up from my seat.
You are so happy, laughing and smiling today.
Yes, I'm very happy because I know that I'm free.
Prophecy Testimony
The man of God said that we are young.
As you can see, I'm young and my wife is very, very young as well.
I married in the year 2015 and to be frank with you, just as I tried to explain to the man of God,
I never tasted what you would call a happy home.
Before I married my wife, I was brought up in a Christian home
and always tried to follow the laws of God.
I prepared myself for this marriage.
There were many women and girls around me
but I separated myself from them for one year in order to look for a good partner.
I remembered this fine, beautiful lady over here.
I decided to give her a phone call.
I called her for the first time and asked her, "Will you marry me? Can you be my wife?"
I married my wife and trouble started.
At the time, my wife was just a young lady; she had just finished secondary school.
As we moved into our house, she would be on social media, always with her phone - busy.
She had no time for me and I talked to her about it.
I asked her to leave the phone for some time so we could talk and reason as husband and wife.
I begged her but she refused to listen.
I told her that what she was doing, I also knew how to do it very well.
If I started my own, it would be fire.
She refused; I gave her time to stop but she refused so then, I started my own.
I brought out my new phone, downloaded WhatsApp, social media and Facebook.
See friend requests from ladies - fine ones.
As I started my own, it became fire.
Nobody was listening to each other anymore.
Ok, let me forget that one.
This happened immediately after we got married.
More especially this year.
That's when I developed another habit of drinking alcohol.
What caused that was too much disrespect - beating me in the sense that I could not talk.
If I talked once, she would reply me twenty times.
If I tried to calm her down as a husband and come near her to ask what the problem was,
she would slap me.
I thank God for being in The SCOAN today because I have been yearning to come here
because I knew the man of God was the only one who could solve this problem.
I thank God for what happened last Sunday.
After the prophecy, I'm very happy with my wife.
Yesterday as we were walking, she held my hand.
Prophecy Testimony
Can you demonstrate what you are saying.
Like this.
You mean, it was strange?
It was strange.
And she was not looking ashamed; she was just focusing on me.
Prophecy Testimony
And you can see now...
If you saw how we were sitting there,
when she got tired, she would rest her head on my shoulder.
I'm very happy.
So you mean, she never used to do all this before?
All these things - before, I did not deserve them.
Instead it was beating...
Yes, if she mistakenly did this and then realised it, she would say, "No, you don't deserve it!"
But I thank God today that I deserve all this.
Amen.
Prophecy Testimony
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Our names are Mr and Mrs Obiora Emmanuel.
Last Sunday, the man of God gave us a prophecy.
It was after the mass prayer; I was sitting on the chair,
resting my head on the chair in front of me
when I heard, "There is a couple here. The wife always beats".
I was like, "Who does that?" I raised up my head to know who the person was.
Then I looked beside me and found out that my husband was no longer
sitting beside me - so it was me.
I was telling myself, "I'm not going out, unless all the ushers will come and carry me out.
I can't see myself standing here. For what now?"
I don't know what made me to just carry my bag.
The two couples sitting next to me - they were big, heavy -
before one could pass them, one would have to say, "Excuse me".
I found out that the space was big for me to pass.
When I came to the front, that is when I realised where I was.
I became more angry like "What is this man saying?"
I was so angry at my husband again.
After the prayer last Sunday, I now see my husband as my husband, unlike before.
Whenever I was close to him, I was always sweating; I don't know why.
Even if it was under aircondition, I would always sweat.
One day I asked him, "Don't you think it was a mistake getting married to you?
See how I am sweating when I'm together with you - imagine that".
And then he said, "You are not normal".
And then I realised, truly, I wasn't normal
because I had a spiritual husband, which I knew.
I kept praying.
I thank God that after everything, I came here and I was delivered.
Praise be to the Lord Jesus!
How did you beat your husband?
Whenever I was angry - everything he did was negative; I didn't see anything positive in him.
Only when he was not around, I would be seeing good.
I would think, "This man is really a good man".
But whenever he came back...
I would be seeing another person.
Whenever he was talking to me, I would think, "Why is he giving me this advice".
Instead of listening to his advice, I would be remembering all I had gone through
and I would just be like, "Leave me alone!
I would just slap him - I would not know where the hand hit him.
Sometimes I would not even know that I beat him; I would ask, "Did I hit you?"
He would say, "No, you didn't hit me".
I thank God for today. Thank you, Man of God.
Prophecy Testimony
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Mel Flowers 20/04/2019
RV Robert Begier 21/04/2019